[{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678918427,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":29266,"timeElapsed":126744},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678935353,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":16924,"timeElapsed":143671},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678946348,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":10992,"timeElapsed":154666},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678952012,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":5662,"timeElapsed":160330},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678960556,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":8542,"timeElapsed":168874},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678974390,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":13832,"timeElapsed":182707},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678980170,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":5778,"timeElapsed":188487},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678991776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":11605,"timeElapsed":200094},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678998469,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":6692,"timeElapsed":206787},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679013566,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":12572,"timeElapsed":221884},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679018881,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5314,"timeElapsed":227199},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679024942,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":6059,"timeElapsed":233260},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679032329,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":7386,"timeElapsed":240647},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679036415,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":4085,"timeElapsed":244733},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679045961,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":9544,"timeElapsed":254279},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679049523,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3560,"timeElapsed":257841},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679056940,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":7415,"timeElapsed":265257},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679061231,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4290,"timeElapsed":269549},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679071064,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9831,"timeElapsed":279381},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679085150,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":12338,"timeElapsed":293468},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679089373,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4221,"timeElapsed":297691},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679095669,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":6296,"timeElapsed":303987},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679103102,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":7431,"timeElapsed":311420},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679108949,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":5845,"timeElapsed":317267},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679115594,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":6643,"timeElapsed":323912},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679120342,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":4747,"timeElapsed":328660},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679126737,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":6394,"timeElapsed":335055},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679130404,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3666,"timeElapsed":338722},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679141000,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":8652,"timeElapsed":349318},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679145090,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4088,"timeElapsed":353408},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679149939,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":4848,"timeElapsed":358257},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679156668,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":6727,"timeElapsed":364986},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679161470,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4800,"timeElapsed":369788},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679168237,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":6766,"timeElapsed":376555},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679172539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4300,"timeElapsed":380857},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679177587,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5048,"timeElapsed":385905},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679181454,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3866,"timeElapsed":389772},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679196775,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":13734,"timeElapsed":405092},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679203019,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6243,"timeElapsed":411337},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679212285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":9264,"timeElapsed":420603},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679218666,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":6380,"timeElapsed":426984},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679223839,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":5172,"timeElapsed":432157},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679227436,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3595,"timeElapsed":435754},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679233444,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":6007,"timeElapsed":441762},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679237627,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":4182,"timeElapsed":445945},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679242963,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":5335,"timeElapsed":451281},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679247897,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4933,"timeElapsed":456215},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679256689,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6972,"timeElapsed":465007},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679261785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5094,"timeElapsed":470103},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679265862,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4075,"timeElapsed":474180},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679270006,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":4143,"timeElapsed":478324},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679275069,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":5062,"timeElapsed":483387},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679280136,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5065,"timeElapsed":488454},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679283012,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2874,"timeElapsed":491330},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679289407,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":6394,"timeElapsed":497725},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679293412,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":4004,"timeElapsed":501730},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679305823,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":10801,"timeElapsed":514141},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679309518,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3694,"timeElapsed":517836},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679316871,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":7352,"timeElapsed":525189},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679325129,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":8257,"timeElapsed":533447},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679329272,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":4142,"timeElapsed":537590},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679335212,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":5939,"timeElapsed":543530},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679339063,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":3850,"timeElapsed":547381},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679343704,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":4639,"timeElapsed":552022},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679349798,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":6092,"timeElapsed":558116},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679361156,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":9678,"timeElapsed":569474},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679365001,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3844,"timeElapsed":573319},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679370659,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":5656,"timeElapsed":578977},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679374076,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":3416,"timeElapsed":582394},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679377032,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2955,"timeElapsed":585350},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679384178,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":7144,"timeElapsed":592496},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679388035,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3856,"timeElapsed":596353},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679396960,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":8924,"timeElapsed":605278},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679400114,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3152,"timeElapsed":608432},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679408503,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":6703,"timeElapsed":616821},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679411946,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3441,"timeElapsed":620264},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679417080,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":5132,"timeElapsed":625398},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679422778,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":5696,"timeElapsed":631096},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679426419,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3640,"timeElapsed":634737},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679434323,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":7903,"timeElapsed":642641},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679438344,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4019,"timeElapsed":646662},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679443941,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5596,"timeElapsed":652259},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679448380,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4437,"timeElapsed":656698},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679458858,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":8939,"timeElapsed":667175},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679462158,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3299,"timeElapsed":670476},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679466102,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3942,"timeElapsed":674420},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679470272,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":4168,"timeElapsed":678590},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679473942,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3668,"timeElapsed":682260},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679478458,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4515,"timeElapsed":686776},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679481380,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2921,"timeElapsed":689698},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679499600,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":18218,"timeElapsed":707918},{"subjectID":"ya2cf109oa","prolificID":"665ddf309813ddc0869e8780","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b41e6b3716c11cd2c64","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679535545,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":35944,"timeElapsed":743863}]